So in this quick video, we are going to see how we can install Arduino IDE.
You can install Arduino IDE by going on this link.
The link will be provided in the resources file as well, and you can download Arduino IDE according
to your environment.
Like I'm using Windows so I can download Windows form of Arduino IDE and similarly there is Mac OS and
Linux versions as well.
White, so I have already downloaded Ardino and installed it.
It's quite simple, so let me open it.
You can install it with few clicks.
So after installing Arduino ID, all you have to do is you have to go into sketch and include libraries
and manage libraries.
Right?
So we are going to install library for RC 5 to 2 module which we are going to use for mifare classic
cards.
Right.
So all you have to do is you have to type mf RC.
5 to 2 and you will find these libraries, right?
And I have already installed these libraries, as you can see over here.
So you can see these libraries are installed, right?
So all you have to do is you have to install this libraries and you are done.
And in the next video we are going to see how we can find Uuid of Mifare classic cards using Arduino,
Uno and RC 5 to 2 module.